LEVAN VEKUA

212.203.6800 | levelua@gmail.com | Brooklyn, NY 11235 | levelua@gmail.com | Brooklyn, NY 11235 | levelua@gmail.com | Brooklyn, NY 11235 | levelua@gmail.com | Brooklyn, NY 11235 | levelua.com | levelua.

SUMMARY

Offering 10+ years of progressive experience in owning web-based projects from concept and design through testing, implementation and client updates. Diligent about producing exceptionally clean, strong and secure code. Successful at achieving browser, device and operating system compatibility objectives while satisfying client desires and producing robust, sophisticated designs.

SKILLS

- Design: Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Figma.
- Code: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Build: Magento M1-M2, Shopify, Wordpress, Salesforce.
- Process: Sass, Gulp, Grunt.
- Deploy: Git, GitHub, Capistrano, Jenkins.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer, R/West, December 2020 - Current | Portland, OR

- Working on multiple projects and platforms: Magento M2, Shopify+, Wordpress.
- Performing UI updates, content maintenance and optimization.
- Developing marketing campaigns, conducting QA and reporting.
- Bringing mock-ups to life with HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Designing visual and graphic assets to use on multiple platforms and resolutions.

Front End Developer, OAK, February 2010 - May 2019 | Brooklyn, NY

- \bullet Magento M1 e-commerce site design update and maintenance.
- User journey and usability enhancement, performance and SEO optimization.
- Responsive landing page designs, Wordpress blog layout updates and Ul improvements.
- Improved and designed new layouts to achieve usability and performance objectives.

Front End Developer, Nili Lotan, August 2017 - October 2018 | New York, NY

- Website redesign, optimisation, UI/UX implementation for mobile/desktop screens.
- Third party plugin integration and customisation.
- · Collaborated with project and product managers to set goals and scope projects.
- Translated mock-ups to functional HTML CSS and JavaScript interfacecs.

Front End Developer, Alexander Wang, May 2016 - September 2016 | New York, NY

- Worked with product manager to develop and implement responsive lookbooks.
- Applied custom script for interface animation and end-user interaction.
- Colaborated with product managers and designers to implement UI features.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Associate Web Master New England Tech January 2003